indiaproperty.com 2018-03-08

# Property - Real Estate - India Property - Properties India - Property Sites

Privacy Statement

Indiaproperty.com is an online property portal endeavoring constantly to provide you with premium property services. Since we are strongly committed to your right to privacy, we have drawn out a privacy statement with regard to the information we collect from you.

What information you need to give in to use this site? 

We gather information from members and guests who apply for the various services our site offers. It includes, but may not be limited to, email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, mailing address, zip code and telephone number or fax number. We also collect additional information about your property. 

How the site uses the information it collects/tracks?

Indiaproperty.com collects information from our clients primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver personalized experience. 

With whom the site shares the information it collects/tracks? 

The information collected from any of our clients is shared with their approval to individuals and organizations. IndiaProperty.com does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. We may disclose to third party services certain personally identifiable information such as name, email, mobile number and information we collect as you access and use our service, including device information, location and network carrier. This information is shared with third party service providers so that we can personalize the app for you and perform behavioral analytics. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security and revealed unless you want it to. We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.

Can users contact Builders, Agents, Brokers and others? 

If the Builder, Agent/Broker or any individual has provided their contact information for everyone to see then users can contact them at their request.

Notice

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments or as a result of a change of policy in our company. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement, please write in to [privacy@indiaproperty.com.](mailto:privacy@indiaproperty.com)

__TOP
